i've written a few words this is for the proletariat all you had to do was pay us enough
to live said the man behind the cam before the flame was lit push come to shove come
from above to where the labor lives down on the bottom but the problems where the board members
sit executives are ruling class at last and cash system i need to deck them in the halls
they never see the people coming even when they from us they never feel the power humming because
it's from within us indigenous autochthonous ruled by the moon before the dollar was the idol before
there was a bible before we were all trained to walk single file and pledge allegiance to politicians
communal vision i hope you're listening i hope you're listening because buddy with that lighter
at the end of his rope will do more than murder because the supply chain choked that warehouse was
a burial ground of desires futures flew free as the flames grew higher higher higher higher
higher futures grew free as the flames flew higher higher higher higher we deserve more big ups to
everybody organizing around the world because the workers are where the power lives oh and AI